<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<categories>
	<category id="1" name="About The Top" screenName="ABOUT THE TOP">
		<questions>
			<question id="1">
				<q><para>Q: What exactly can I expect when I visit Top of the Rock?</para></q>
				<a><para>A: A first class experience. You enter on 50th Street between 5th and 6th Avenue. If you have your ticket, 
				you will be directed up the stairs to the mezzanine and enter the pre-show area.  If not, you'll need to stop at		 
				our box office to get a ticket.</para>
				<para>Once in the pre-show area, you may tour our multi-media theater exhibit where you can 
				enjoy our educational displays. Then, you can proceed to the sky shuttles which will take you from the mezzanine to the 
				67th floor observation deck.  The atmosphere at Top of the Rock is one of comfortable elegance, echoing the classic art 
				deco style of Rockefeller Center, while moving boldly into the future. The observation deck itself is split into three levels, 
				the first of which is enclosed, with two open-air terraces. The second two are open. The third level, the 70th floor, has a 
				particularly majestic, unobstructed, 360 degree view of New York City and beyond.</para>
				<para>The "Joie" Crystal Chandelier in the atrium of the main entrance, the "Radiance" Geode Crystal Wall, and the Target
				&#174 Breezeway are three of our exciting attractions that should not be missed.</para>
				</a>
			</question>
		
		
			<question id="2">
				<q><para>Q:  What time is the first elevator to the TotR?</para></q>
				<a><para>A:  Sky Shuttle elevators begin running at 8:30am and the last shuttle goes up at 11:00 pm.</para></a>
			</question>
			
			<question id="3">
				<q><para>Q:  How long does it take to get to the Top?</para></q>
				<a><para>A: Our Sky Shuttle elevators bring you up in a "New York Minute", 50 seconds!</para></a>
			</question>
			
			<question id="4">
				<q><para>Q: Is there a restaurant and/or bar at TotR?</para></q>
				<a><para>A:  There is not a restaurant or bar located at TotR, but there are many dining options on 
				the concourse level of 30 Rockefeller Plaza where you will be exiting the elevators.  
				There are also many restaurants in the general vicinity.</para></a>
			</question>
			
			<question id="5">
				<q><para>Q: When was the Observation Deck first opened?</para></q>
				<a><para>A: It was initially opened in 1933, and consisted of the 69th and 70th floors. It was originally designed
				to evoke the upper decks of a 1930s grand ocean liner, outfitted with deck chairs, gooseneck fixtures, and large 
				air-conditioning vents intended to look like the stacks on a  ship's deck. </para></a>
			</question>
			
			<question id="6">
				<q><para>Q: When did the Observation Deck close/reopen?</para></q>
				<a><para>A: The deck was closed in 1986, when renovations to the Rainbow Room made it difficult for 
				large groups to access the space. It was reopened on November 1, 2005, after being remodeled and reinvented 
				for the 21st Century.</para></a>
			</question>
			
			<question id="7">
				<q><para>Q: How many levels are there to the Observation Deck? How big is it?</para></q>\
				<a><para>A: Top of the Rock is a 3-tiered observation deck on the 67th, 69th, and 70th floors of Rockefeller 
				center. It has a surface area of 55,000 square-feet (5,110 m2) and the upper decks are 850 feet (260 m) above 
				the street level.</para></a>
			</question>
				
			<question id="8">
				<p><para>Q: Can you see the Rockefeller Center Christmas Tree or Skating Rink from the Top of the Rock?</para></p>
				<a><para>A: Unfortunately, no. Both attractions are too close to the building to be seen from the Observation Deck. 
				However, both are easily accessible from the Concourse retail shop where our Sky Shuttles drop you off after your return from the Top.
				</para></a>
			</question>
			
			<question id="9">
				<q><para>Q: What am I looking at? Which building is which?</para></q>
				<a><para>A: We have viewfinder maps, which detail the skyline, available at our retail kiosks. 
				Our Hosts are also happy to assist you in locating New York landmarks.</para></a>
			</question>
			
			<question id="10">
				<p><para>Q: When is the best time to come to Top of the Rock?</para></p>
				<a><para>A: That's fairly subjective based on personal taste. Mornings and afternoons give you an unmatched view of
				Central Park, while night gives you the New York skyline in lights. One of our more popular times, particularly for 
				couples, is dusk. The Observation Deck provides a unique vantage point as the sun sets beyond the Hudson River. 
				If your question of time is because you are concerned about line length, we highly advise advance ticket 
				sales. </para></a>
			</question>
			
			<question id="11">
				<p><para>Q. Does Top of the Rock host private parties or corporate events?</para></p>
				<a><para>A: We offer a variety of options for event planners, and our event space is a masterwork of design 
				with the stunning backdrop of the New York City skyline. If you are interested in planning a Special Event, 
				you are welcome to contact our Special Event Sales Team at 212-698-2000 for details.</para></a>
			</question>
		</questions>

	</category>
</categories>

		
	
