<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<categories>
	<category id="2" name="Design and Special Features" screenName="DESIGN &#38 SPECIAL FEATURES">
		<questions>
			<question id="12">
				<q><para>Q: Who is the architect behind the renovations of Top of the Rock?</para></q>
				<a><para>Michael Gabellini, the renowned namesake of Manhattan firm Gabellini Associates, designed Top of the Rock. 
				His design echoes the classic Art Deco styling of Rockefeller Center, while moving boldly into the future, 
				seamlessly incorporating high-tech developments into our venue space. Gabellini's design work ensures that the 
				New York skyline is not the only breath-taking view at the Top.</para></a>
			</question>
		
		
			<question id="13">
				<q><para>Q: Who made the chandelier in the TotR lobby?</para></q>
				<a><para>A: The 14,000 piece chandelier, Joie, is the largest ever made by Swarovski, 
				one of Top of the Rock’s sponsors. It weighs 5000 lbs, and took 100 people to install in our 
				grand atrium. Its design is meant to emulate both a waterfall, and the shape of 30 Rockefeller 
				Center turned upside-down. It was recently featured on the cover of Interior Design Magazine.</para></a>
			</question>
			
			<question id="14">
				<q><para>Q: Is it true you have a crystal wall on the Observation Deck?</para></q>
				<a><para>A: Radiance, created by German artist and designer Michael Hammers, is the first crystal 
				wall of its kind, a massive geode wall that is 180 feet wide and 9 feet tall. It is one of the highlights 
				of the 67th floor of Top of the Rock. The wall consists of 600 custom-designed glass panels simulating faceted 
				crystals -- covered by colored,	mouth-blown glass and featuring fiber optic lighting.  110 of the glass panels 
				feature Swarovski crystal clusters.</para></a>
			</question>
			
			<question id="15">
				<q><para>Q: What is the Target® Breezeway?</para></q>
				<a><para>A: On the 69th floor of the Observation Deck, Target® adds its own cool and imaginative style to 
				the Observation Deck with the Target® Breezeway, a cutting edge experience that puts a human touch on 
				motion-detection technology, using the movements of our guests as its catalyst. It needs to be seen to be believed.</para></a>
			</question>
			
			<question id="16">
				<q><para>Q: What is the elevator ride like?</para></q>
				<a><para>A: Our Sky Shuttle elevators are a part of the Top of the Rock experience, not merely a means to get to the 
				Observation Deck. In 50 seconds, we’ll whisk you to the Top in style. The Sky Shuttle has a transparent top, 
				allowing the guests to see into the elevator shaft above, as part of a state-of-the-art, multi-media display. 
				You have never experienced an elevator ride quite like this. </para></a>
			</question>
			
			
			
		</questions>

	</category>
</categories>

		
	
