<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<categories>
	<category id="7" name="Online Ticketing" screenName="ONLINE TICKETING">
		<questions>
	
			<question id="37">
				<q><para>Q:  Can I purchase tickets online the day I want to visit TotR?</para></q>
				<a><para>A:  Tickets can be purchased online or on the phone through a sales coordinator three hours 
				or more in advance. Anything less than three hours in advance must be done in person at the box office, 
				open from 8:30 AM -10:50 PM.</para></a>
			</question>
			
			<question id="38">
				<q><para>Q:  What if I can't print the tickets I purchased online?</para></q>
				<a><para>A:  Please present the credit card that was used to purchase the tickets at the ticket counter when you arrive 
				and a sales associate will print the tickets for you. It is recommended that you bring the confirmation number from the 
				first ticket in your purchase. This number is located under the barcode on your ticket.</para></a>
			</question>
			
			<question id="39">
				<q><para>Q. Why didn't I receive a confirmation e-mail?</para></q>
				<a><para>A. Sometimes, our confirmation e-mails are routed to your spam or junk mail folder so you don't see it in your 
				in-box. Another reason may be that the e-mail address was entered incorrectly. If you don't receive a confirmation email 
				within an hour of purchase, feel free to contact us at info@topoftherocknyc.com and one of our customer care representatives 
				will address the issue.</para></a>
			</question>
			
			<question id="40">
				<q><para>Q:  Do I have to print individual tickets for everyone in the party or is there a single pass for the party?</para></q>
				<a><para>A:  You must print tickets for the whole party. Alternately, you can bring the credit card you booked the tickets 
				with you to the box office, along with the confirmation number (located under the barcode) from one of your tickets, 
				and the box office can print your tickets for you.</para></a>
			</question>

			
			
			
			
		</questions>

	</category>
</categories>

		
