<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<categories>
	<category id="12" name="Rockefeller Center" screenName="ROCKEFLLER CENTER">
		<questions>
			
			
			<question id="55">
				<q><para>Q: What else is there to do at Rockefeller Center?</para></q>
				<a><para>A: There are many things to see and do at Rockefeller Center. The Center includes restaurants, shops, 
				artwork, and tours. The Today Show is broadcast live from the plaza regularly, and there are often special 
				events held here. For a more complete listing, including a monthly events calendar, visit http://www.rockefellercenter.com.</para></a>
			</question>
			
			
			<question id="56">
				<q><para>Q: What time does the Rainbow Room open?</para></q>
				<a><para>A: The Rainbow Room opens to the public at 5PM. Reservations are required for dinner, but not for drinks.</para></a>
			</question>
			
			
			<question id="57">
				<q><para>Q: Where do we go for the skating rink?</para></q>
				<a><para>A: The large stairway leading to the rink from the Channel Gardens is the entrance for all rink guests. 
				For rates and more information on the skating rink, please visit their website at http://www.therinkatrockcenter.com. </para></a>
			</question>
			
			
			<question id="58">
				<q><para>Q: When is the Rockefeller Center Christmas Tree lighting ceremony for 2006?</para></q>
				<a><para>A: The Christmas Tree is lit after Thanksgiving every year. A definite date for 2006 
				has not yet been announced, but the tentative date is Tuesday, November 28th.</para></a>
			</question>
			
			<question id="59">
				<q><para>Q: Where do we find the Rockefeller Center Tour and NBC Studio Tour?</para></q>
				<a><para>A: Both tours leave from the NBC Experience Store in 30 Rockefeller Plaza, and are great companion experiences 
				to Top of the Rock. The Rockefeller Center Tour focuses on the art and architecture of Rockefeller Center, 
				while the NBC Studio Tour brings you through the studios used to tape shows such as <ital>Saturday Night Live</ital>
				and <ital>Late Night with Conan O'Brien</ital>. Both tours are particularly well complemented by the Pre-Show exhibit 
				at Top of the Rock and the short films on the history of the Rockefeller Center.</para></a>
			</question>
			
			<question id="60">
				<q><para>Q: Where do we find the Radio City Music Hall Stage Door Tour?</para></q>
				<a><para>A: Radio City Music Hall, right across 50th Street from the main Top of the Rock entrance, plays host to the Stage Door Tour,
				which is perfectly paired with the short film Top of the Rock offers on the history of Radio City and the Rockettes. </para></a>
			</question>
		
			<question id="61">
				<q><para>Q: Where is the Diego Rivera mural?</para></q>
				<a><para>A: <ital>Man in the Crossroads</ital>, a mural by Mexican painter Diego Rivera, was originally on the wall 
				behind the information desk in the lobby of the 30 Rockefeller Plaza. It was removed in 1937 over controversy regarding a picture 
				of Vladimir Lenin in the mural. It was replaced by <ital>American Progress</ital>, a mural by Spaniard Jose Maria Sert, 
				which adorns the wall now.</para>
				
				<para>Renewed public interest in the story of the Rivera mural came on the heels of the movie, <ital>Frida</ital>. 
				Its just one thread of the rich tapestry of art history at Rockefeller Center. That tradition, begun with the 
				artistic vision of Abby Aldrich-Rockefeller, continues with Tishman Speyer in the modern era. 
				Top of the Rock, and its masterfully crafted architecture, is the next stage in that tradition.</para></a>
			</question>
			

			
		</questions>

	</category>
</categories>

		
