<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<categories>
	<category id="5" name="Ticketing" screenName="TICKETING">
		<questions>
			<question id="24">
				<q><para>Q: How does the ticketing work?</para></q>
				<a><para>A: If the tickets were purchased in advance, then the tickets can be printed out from the 
				confirmation e-mail. This allows the ticket holder to bypass the ticket counter and proceed to the 
				pre-show area on the mezzanine. If you would like to walk-in and purchase tickets without reservations, 
				you will be reserved in the next available time slot to enter the pre-show area.</para></a>
			</question>
		
		
			<question id="25">
				<q><para>Q:  Am I required to purchase tickets in advance?
				</para></a>
				<a><para>A:  Advanced reservations are suggested, but not required.For your convenience, there are three ways you can purchase 
				tickets for Top of the Rock </para>
				<para>1. You can purchase online at http://www.topoftherocknyc.com. </para>
				<para>2. Or you can also walk up to the box office located on 50th Street between 5th and 6th Avenue.</para> 
				<para>3. You can contact our box office at 1-877-NYC-ROCK.</a></para>
			</question>
			
			<question id="26">
				<q><para>Q. If I have my tickets printed out do I still have to stand in line?</para></q>
				<a><para>A. If you already have your tickets, you may bypass the ticket line and proceed up the stairs to the pre-show area.
				</para></a>
			</question>
			
			<question id="27">
				<q><para>Q:  What do the times on the tickets mean?</para></q>
				<a><para>A:  The first time on your ticket is your time slot to enter the pre-show area. The second time on your ticket is 
				when you exit the pre-show area and board a shuttle to the Observation Deck.  Once you are at the on the deck you may stay 
				as long as you wish until we close at Midnight.</para></a>
			</question>
			
					
			<question id="28">
				<q><para>Q:  Are children under 6 admitted for free?</para></q>
				<a><para>A:  Yes, admittance for children under 6 years old is free when accompanied by their parent or legal guardian.  
				This does not apply to school groups.  </para></a>
			</question>
			
			<question id="29">
				<q><para>Q:  What if I show up late and miss my timeslot?</para></q>
				<a><para>A:  Because our focus is on excellent customer service, we will honor the ticket on the same day 
				and will book you for the next available timeslot. You will not need to purchase a new ticket. 
				However, we strongly suggest arriving at the time listed on your ticket for an optimal experience.</para></a>
			</question>
			
			<question id="30">
				<q><para>Q: What if I show up early for my timeslot?</para></q>
				<a><para>A: If we have available space, we will attempt to accommodate you in the next available timeslot. 
				However, if we are sold out, you will be asked to return at the time on your ticket.</para></a>
			</question>
			
			<question id="31">
				<q><para>Q:  Can you send tickets by post?</para></q>
				<a><para>A: We do not send tickets by post; if you are unable to print out the tickets from the e-mail or you do not have e-mail, 
				you can present your credit card at the ticket counter and we will print your tickets for you. </para></a>
			</question>
			
			<question id="32">
				<q><para>Q:  Does our reservation expire? </para></q>
				<a><para>A:  Your tickets will expire after the time printed on the ticket. </para></a>
			</question>
			
			<question id="33">
				<q><para>Q: Do you offer a yearly pass, or a ticket that allows more than one visit per day?</para></q>
				<a><para>A: While both ideas have been suggested, and are under consideration, we do not offer either at this time.</para></a>
			</question>

			
			
		</questions>

	</category>
</categories>

		
